class Flashcard {
  final String question;
  final String answer;

  Flashcard({required this.question, required this.answer});
}

List<Flashcard> quesAnsList = [
  Flashcard(question: "Katze", answer: "Cat"),
  Flashcard(question: "Hund", answer: "Dog"),
  Flashcard(question: "Tasche", answer: "Bag"),
  Flashcard(question: "Tisch", answer: "Table"),
  Flashcard(question: "Frau", answer: "Lady"),
  Flashcard(question: "Mann", answer: "Man"),
  Flashcard(question: "Matte", answer: "Mat"),
  Flashcard(question: "Stuhl", answer: "Chair"),
  Flashcard(question: "Schrank", answer: "Cupboard"),
  Flashcard(question: "Regal", answer: "Shelf"),
];
